SUBHAJIT PAUL

REACT JS | FLUTTER | JAVA SPRING BOOT | FULL-STACK DEVELOPER



- +91-8016970670
- psubhajit14@gmail.com
- Newtown, Kolkata, West Bengal Pin -700157
- https://github.com/psubhajit14

PROFILE

Full stack web developer with 3+ years of experience in building data intensive web applications with React JS and Spring Boot with SQL server. I have built few Flutter project. I have in depth understanding of the complete SDLC with skills in HTML5, CSS, Javascript, React JS, Redux, Web API, Java Spring Boot, Flutter, Dart JS, SQL, Git., JIRA

SKILLS

- React JS
- Redux
- Flutter
- Javascript
- Java Spring Boot
- SQL server, PL/ SQL
- Unit Testing (Enzyme, JUnit)
- · Problem-Solving
- Project Management Tools (JIRA, Git)
- Strong Communication

EXPERIENCE

SPECIALIST PROGRAMMER (SP)

infosys. Limited

FEB 2022 - Present

DIGITAL SPECIALIST ENGINEER (DSE)

infosys. Limited 2021 - 2022

SYSTEM ENGINEER SPECIALIST (SES)

infosys. Limited

2020 - 2021

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY

BP Poddar Institute of Management And Technology

2016 - 2020 DGPA - 8.68

RESPONSIBILITIES

- In Infosys I have worked for a automobile dept. client as a React and Spring Full-Stack Developer. In their internal application used for car pricing and configuration which works in different phases in the supply chain.
- I implemented different batch Job and UI Screen for generating report which helped client to reduce workflow also validate and process data correctly.
- Also handled junior team members to support them in their work.

PROJECTS I HAVE WORKED ON

Relaxation App

- A music player app that uses local storage music files to play music.
- It has extensive features like: explore songs by album, use of playlist, background play.
- You can check the demo: https://github.com/psubhajit14/relaxation-app

GPRAC

- A web application that is created for local people to get acknowledgement
- It supports PWA, RazorPay Payment Integration. Firebase Authentication, Cloud store,
- Multiple Language support (English & Bengali)
- Technology used: React JS, Firebase. Typescript, Node, Express JS, RazorPay API, Ant Design
- You can check the website: https://grpac-mern-grpac.vercel.app/
- You can check the repository: https://github.com/psubhajit14/grpac_mern/